Ah!
啊
Hey! Will you look at that!
嘿 看看这个
Whoa! What's happening?
哇 发生了什么
No, they turned it on!
不要啊 他们把开关打开了
Oh! Never seen this before.
哦 以前从没见到过
Ah!
啊
My face! My beautiful face!
我的脸 我美丽的脸
-What is going on?! -We are abstracting!
-发生了什么 -我们在抽象化
There are four stages. This is the first.
一共有四个阶段 这是第一个
Nonobjective fragmentation!
抽象碎片化
Alright, do not panic what is important is that we all stay together.
好的 别紧张  重要的是我们都在一起
Aw!
啊
-Ah! -We are at second stage!
-啊 -我们在第二阶段了
We are deconstructing!
我们正在解构
Run!
跑啊
Aw! I can't feel my legs!
嗷 我感觉不到我的腿了
Oh, there they are.
哦 他们在这儿呢
Come here! Me!
到这儿来 我
Aw! We got to get out of here! Aw!
嗷 我们得赶紧出去 嗷
Before we're not even shape and color! Aw!
趁我们还不是平面和颜色
We'll get stuck here forever!
否则我们会永远被关在这里
Bong! Why do we come in here?
冰棒 我们为什么要进这里
I told you! It's a short cut!
我告诉过你 这是条捷径
The train.
火车